Hey, good morning.
When did you finally come to bed?
Because I thought you were coming right up,
but then I fell asleep.
Yeah, the game.
It was amazing.
Because I thought we had plans.
Sorry.
Did you catch the end of that game?
See?
All right.
Well, I'll let you boys talk about your exciting sports.
I just hope there's not a game on tonight.
Sex.
Oh.
Because I thought we had plans.
I think she just gave me the look.
I thought it meant gas.
so i stayed up to watch instead of going upstairs and now instead of being mad deborah gave me the
I think she just gave me the look.
Huh.
maybe tomorrow
so she doesn't take me for granted you know
look again huh maybe maybe i should turn her down again you know why would you do a silly thing like
that i don't know i mean i'm always the one being shot down it felt good her wondering where i was
last night you can't turn her down i could turn her down oh come on you'll follow her around like
Hey, good morning.
a dog with his tongue hanging out yeah your tongue is the leash she uses to parade you around the
I think she just gave me the look.
park ladies and gentlemen worst in show yeah well then uh maybe that's why i should turn her down
Yeah, the game.
so she doesn't take me for granted you know
i mean she's got to appreciate what she's got here yes you're quite a catch
i can hardly keep my hands off you
When did you finally come to bed?
God.
Hey.
oh i left the hallway light on
i'll be right back
i can say no i can say no
you
uh-oh
you must be tired oh yeah i'm kind of beat you know i just i got a lot of stuff
Huh.
going on
maybe tomorrow
really
yeah
okay
well night yeah oh good night
yeah
Hey, good morning.
When did you finally come to bed?
wait man come on let's go uh i don't think i'm gonna go hit balls today
what oh why did the wife say you can't go no no it's just uh just a little stiff that's all
oh
so it's a medical decision you're making to stay here and helping me pick out drapes
no sale
ah drapes yeah well there's any material left over once you make yourself a little skirt
i'm still gonna go and you know what i may go tomorrow because i can do whatever i want
What do you mean?
what do you mean all right
you thought i couldn't turn down deborah right two times my friend
that's good
last night i told her that i had a lot of work to do today
work
and then and then first thing this morning she started hinting again
she even brushed your teeth and everything
no sale