Ha!
Hi, Ray!
Oh, hey.
Oh, uh, Deb's not here.
She's out with the kids, so I'm just, you know,
trying to make the best of it.
Yeah.
Come.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I'm just gonna watch the Nick game, you know,
and, uh, nothing else.
Great.
Yeah, Robert called and told me you guys were gonna watch the game
when he got home from work,
so I thought I'd wait for him over here.
Is that okay?
Oh, yeah, sure. Yeah.
All right.
So, so, uh,
when did Robert say he was gonna come home?
About an hour.
Are you excited about what's next?
Yeah.
A fondue date night?
What, what, what, what?
You guys are coming over tomorrow night
for Amy's first annual fondue night.
It's gonna be just the three of our own couples.
Like a triple date.
Hey.
Yeah, a date with my parents.
I know you think it's corny, but it'll be fun.
Really.
Fondue date night.
Yeah.
You don't want to, uh,
talk to Robert about it
when he gets here in, uh, 58 minutes.
May I?
Oh. Oh, yeah.
Oh, look,
this one looks like a heart.
So from now on,
that's where I'm buying all my sweaters.
There he is.
Hey, there he is. There he is.
Hi, sweetie.
Missed you.
Yeah, what's up? We've been waiting an hour and 11 minutes.
Uh, Amy,
Ma wanted me to remind you that you'll be making the salad
for the dinner tonight.
Oh, I forgot. I better go. Darn.
Yeah, damn it.
See you later, Yogi.
And Ray, I'll see you
at fondue.
Okay, yeah.
This is such a cutie pie.
Yeah.
Oh, it's the second half already?
Yeah, man. You're missing some great basketball.
Yeah.
Actually, I kind of missed some, too.
It was, uh, me and Amy,
we had a nice, long
chat.
All right. That's really nice.
What did you guys talk about?
Oh, gosh, pretty much everything, I think.
Uh, Amy's great, huh?
Yeah, Amy's great. She's great.
Yeah.
She's kind of like a little
Lady Chatterley.
Lady Chatterley?
Yeah. What do you mean?
Oh, you know, like, she always
wants to know where everybody is,
and she gets real excited about fondue
date night.
And she told me about this interesting sales girl
and told her a sweater and, you know,
whatever. It's all good stuff.
It's all good.
Are you saying that Amy talks too much?
No, Robert, I love Amy.
Wow, are you a liar.
You know, I know what it is.
I got something good, and you can't stand it.
Oh, you never could. Remember when I made
that diorama in Mr. Carolyn's history class?
What?
Everybody said how great it was.
Everybody!
I won a prize, remember?
But you said it stunk.
You had George Washington fighting a dinosaur.
It was a dragon, Raymond!
A dragon that represented
years of British tyranny!
Which just goes to show how stupid
you were then and now.
Uh, Robert, I didn't...
Everybody!
So you have to tell me that she's a lady
chatterbox who won't shut up?
I know how it goes.
Jealous
ass.
Jealous!
Yes!
Stop it. No.
No, come on. Don't go, Robert.
Stay. Stay and watch the game.
Come on. You want to say something
bad about my wife, you can. I don't care.
Oh, come on.
Say it.
She's a bad cook and she's mean.
Hey.
All right.
All right. One second. One second.
And you may think that, Robert,
but you'll be dead wrong.
Dead wrong!
Deborah is a caring,
beautiful, skinny person.