Hey, good morning.
When did you finally come to bed?
Because I thought you were coming right up,
but then I fell asleep.
Yeah, the game.
It was amazing.
Because I thought we had plans.
Sorry.
Did you catch the end of that game?
See?
All right.
Well, I'll let you boys talk about your exciting sports.
I just hope there's not a game on tonight.
Sex.
Oh.
it's weird though it's weird okay last night i got the look but i i got caught up in the game
so i stayed up to watch instead of going upstairs and now instead of being mad deborah gave me the
look again huh maybe maybe i should turn her down again you know why would you do a silly thing like
that i don't know i mean i'm always the one being shot down it felt good her wondering where i was
last night you can't turn her down i could turn her down oh come on you'll follow her around like
a dog with his tongue hanging out yeah your tongue is the leash she uses to parade you around the
park ladies and gentlemen worst in show yeah well then uh maybe that's why i should turn her down
so she doesn't take me for granted you know
i mean she's got to appreciate what she's got here yes you're quite a catch
i can hardly keep my hands off you
hey
oh i left the hallway light on
i'll be right back
i can say no i can say no
you
uh-oh
you must be tired oh yeah i'm kind of beat you know i just i got a lot of stuff
going on
maybe tomorrow
really
yeah
okay
well night yeah oh good night
wait man come on let's go uh i don't think i'm gonna go hit balls today
what oh why did the wife say you can't go no no it's just uh just a little stiff that's all
oh
so it's a medical decision you're making to stay here and helping me pick out drapes
ah drapes yeah well there's any material left over once you make yourself a little skirt
i'm still gonna go and you know what i may go tomorrow because i can do whatever i want
what do you mean all right
you thought i couldn't turn down deborah right two times my friend
that's good
last night i told her that i had a lot of work to do today
work
and then and then first thing this morning she started hinting again
she even brushed your teeth and everything
oh it's amazing it's like it's like every time i turn it down she seems to want it more
she's like a guy
huh but she's not getting upset
no no that's just she's so fiscal
She's been treating me better all day.
I came down this morning, she was making me a cheese omelet.
I mean, she hasn't done that since before Allie was born.
I mean, yeah, it had shells in it, but still.
You know what I've discovered?
The power of no.
Oh, the power of no. Give me a break.
Hey, hey, hey, who gets to hit a bucket of balls
in the middle of the day?
Yeah, well, that's just the difference
between me and you, Raymond.
You know, you like to golf by yourself
and have a crappy omelet, while I prefer sex.
No, man, you're not getting it.
Deborah can't keep her hands off me.
It's like with the power of no comes the power of yes.
Uh-huh.
For the first time in my marriage,
I finally know what it's like
to be the one wearing the panties.
You have a wrong.
No, no, no, no, no, no, I don't.
But let me ask you something.
Why do you always feel the need
Because I'm not very good at it.
Not very good at what?
Hey, listen, Robert, he can't go hit balls,
but I was thinking that I'd still go.
Yeah, sure, go. Have a good time.
Hey, you know what?
They got a great hot dog guy there.
You want me to bring you back one?
Hey, you let me be the one to watch your figure.
Let me watch your figure?
That's not funny.
That's right, it's not, and yet it is.
Because she is weak.
Weak for my physique.
Oh.
Oh, don't those look nice?
Yeah.
putting them up yesterday.
Well, he can't handle normal-sized tools
with those giant fingers.
Here, push that curtain over a little
so we don't see his blood.
So what do you think, Deb?
Yeah, they look great.
Deborah, dear, you're being so quiet.
That's not like you.
No, I'm fine.
Do I look different to you?
What do you mean?
Have I drooped?
Drooped?
You know, you try to work out
and yet there still comes a day
when everything just...
I wouldn't know about that.
Oh, stop it, Deb.
You look great.
Water aerobics at the Y.
Oh, well, I'll have to check and see if I'm free.
Oh, well, have a ball.
Let me go look for an extra pair of nose clips
and a swim cap.
Deb, are you really upset about this?
Ray keeps turning me down.
What do you mean?
Yeah.
That doesn't sound like him.
I know.
I'm sure it's not you.
I wish he was.
Oh, man.
I should just go with Marie to the Y,
or a swim cap,
Hey, you know,
because last night when Robert and I went to bed,
he was acting kind of distant, too.
But then I just kissed his neck,
and he said, Ray's crazy.
He did?
And then he said something about how I could have all the power.
It was weird.
I mean, why would he s...
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
I know.
Well, that's gross.
Of course, I am.
You know, the worst part about this is that it worked.
I've been trying to make myself look better for him.
Do you know I did 138 sit ups this morning all for some guy whose stomach looks like
a deflated clown balloon?
Boy, boy.
You're gonna kill him, aren't you?
No.
Hey, Jimmy Jack.
Hey. How was work?
Good. Where are the kids?
I sent them over to the Parker's.
Why?
I wanted them out of the house.
Oh, yeah?
I didn't think it would be appropriate for the children
to see what I was going to do to you.
Right now, I don't know.
I mean, I got a lot to do.
Really, Deb, I think...
Yeah, yeah, well...
Okay, look, I'm really starting to feel a little uncomfortable.
What's with you?
Robert told Amy why you've been turning me down.
So you were just toying with me?
Getting me to beg for sex?
That makes you feel good?
No. No, I don't know. I just...
I guess I wanted to see what it was like
to be the one being pursued for once.
But you made me feel terrible about myself.
You just kept rejecting me.
How could you do that to somebody?
You had me convinced I was a fat, ugly old lady.
Well, now you know how I feel.
You feel bad because I turned you down, what, three times?
Try being rejected 40 or 50 times every year
for the last ten years.
How do you think that feels?
You're looking at the president
Welcome. Have a doughnut.
And I say yes a lot.
Exactly. You say yes, and you say no.
You're the bouncer.
You're the bouncer in front of the disco
who decides who gets in and who doesn't.
And for once, it was you standing outside.
Yeah, and you couldn't take it.
Yeah, it's cold out there, isn't it?
Standing in the rain with your bad shirt
and your acne pimples.
There is no way you can compare me turning you down
with what you did to me.
Listen, Ray, if I turn you down,
of three kids all day and thinking
Still using the kids, huh?
Oh, my God.
I don't think I ever wanted to have sex with you.
Yeah, well, you don't have to worry,
because I'm not sure the next time
Oh, you're threatening me with no sex, please.
Yeah, you will be saying please.
I'm serious.
You are always in the mood.
You wouldn't last a night.
I just did three nights, Lady Pantaloons.
Okay, so we'll see who can't last.
Oh, my.
How will I ever resist my baser instincts?
Yeah, I like that.
I like the Southern thing.
That'll be good when you come back saying
Okay, well, good enough.
Ugh.
Oh, my God.
Are those silk?
You want a feel?
It's quite all right.
What's with all your lacy apparel?
Nothing.
Good night.
Yeah.
I'm a little tired, too.
Did you put oil on?
No.
What are you doing?
Me?
What'd you have my mom put on?
Your makeup on?
No sex for you.
¶¶
All right, you win!
What?
I give up!
I am officially asking you to please
What are you talking about?
Our thing!
Our not-having-sex thing!
Of course we're still doing it.
It's been 26 days of doing it.
Not doing it!
Yeah, right!
I can't believe it, but really,
I totally forgot.
You expect me to believe that you didn't realize
that we went 26 days without having sex?
I've been really busy.
The PTA fundraiser is coming up.
26 days?
You weren't even trying.
Guess I was never really close to having the power,
was I?
All this time,
I thought you were doing all those
little things to torture me.
What things?
Forget it.
No, come on.
No, like biting your lower lip
when you use the remote to change the channel.
Or how about when you keep
one of your legs outside of the covers
and the pajama rides up it?
That's just because I'm hot.
Even when you sleep,
every so often you kind of sigh a little.
You haven't slept much lately, have you?
Even now,
look at you,
with your hair like that,
with your...
robe.
What a mess!
Yeah, well,
What?
You just got a little of your power back.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.
Are you toying with me?
Because if you are,
I've been waiting for this for a long time, too, Ray.
it's been 27 days, not 26.
Remember.
Morning, kids.
Well, you live here.
No!
Hey, you guys can make breakfast yourself, right?
Eh?