Ha!
Hi, Ray!
Oh, hey.
Oh, uh, Deb's not here.
She's out with the kids, so I'm just, you know,
trying to make the best of it.
Yeah.
Come.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I'm just gonna watch the Nick game, you know,
and, uh, nothing else.
Great.
Yeah, Robert called and told me you guys were gonna watch the game
when he got home from work,
so I thought I'd wait for him over here.
Is that okay?
Oh, yeah, sure. Yeah.
All right.
So, so, uh,
when did Robert say he was gonna come home?
About an hour.
Are you excited about what's next?
Yeah.
A fondue date night?
What, what, what, what?
You guys are coming over tomorrow night
for Amy's first annual fondue night.
It's gonna be just the three of our own couples.
Like a triple date.
Hey.
Yeah, a date with my parents.
I know you think it's corny, but it'll be fun.
Really.
Fondue date night.
Yeah.
You don't want to, uh,
talk to Robert about it
when he gets here in, uh, 58 minutes.
May I?
Oh. Oh, yeah.
Oh, look,
this one looks like a heart.
So from now on,
that's where I'm buying all my sweaters.
There he is.
Hey, there he is. There he is.
Hi, sweetie.
Missed you.
Yeah, what's up? We've been waiting an hour and 11 minutes.
Uh, Amy,
Ma wanted me to remind you that you'll be making the salad
for the dinner tonight.
Oh, I forgot. I better go. Darn.
Yeah, damn it.
See you later, Yogi.
And Ray, I'll see you
at fondue.
Okay, yeah.
This is such a cutie pie.
Yeah.
Oh, it's the second half already?
Yeah, man. You're missing some great basketball.
Yeah.
Actually, I kind of missed some, too.
It was, uh, me and Amy,
we had a nice, long
chat.
All right. That's really nice.
What did you guys talk about?
Oh, gosh, pretty much everything, I think.
Uh, Amy's great, huh?
Yeah, Amy's great. She's great.
Yeah.
She's kind of like a little
Lady Chatterley.
Lady Chatterley?
Yeah. What do you mean?
Oh, you know, like, she always
wants to know where everybody is,
and she gets real excited about fondue
date night.
And she told me about this interesting sales girl
and told her a sweater and, you know,
whatever. It's all good stuff.
It's all good.
Are you saying that Amy talks too much?
No, Robert, I love Amy.
Wow, are you a liar.
You know, I know what it is.
I got something good, and you can't stand it.
Oh, you never could. Remember when I made
that diorama in Mr. Carolyn's history class?
What?
Everybody said how great it was.
Everybody!
I won a prize, remember?
But you said it stunk.
You had George Washington fighting a dinosaur.
It was a dragon, Raymond!
A dragon that represented
years of British tyranny!
Which just goes to show how stupid
you were then and now.
Uh, Robert, I didn't...
Everybody!
So you have to tell me that she's a lady
chatterbox who won't shut up?
I know how it goes.
Jealous
ass.
Jealous!
Yes!
Stop it. No.
No, come on. Don't go, Robert.
Stay. Stay and watch the game.
Come on. You want to say something
bad about my wife, you can. I don't care.
Oh, come on.
Say it.
She's a bad cook and she's mean.
Hey.
All right.
All right. One second. One second.
And you may think that, Robert,
but you'll be dead wrong.
Dead wrong!
Deborah is a caring,
beautiful, skinny person.
So how's it going?
Oh.
Look, I saved you this chip.
It looks like a heart.
Hi, honey.
Hi.
You've been quiet all night. Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Everything okay with you?
Fine and dandy.
Oh, did I show you this sweater I got?
It's nice.
The sales girl I bought it from, Bridget,
she was so sweet and smart.
She's taking some time off of school to make some money,
but I really hope she finishes because she was really great.
And then you bought the sweater. Got it.
I'm sorry.
Actually, you know, I kind of did have a bad day.
Oh?
What happened?
Oh, nothing. It's just like every other day,
dealing with the scum of the earth.
Well, at least you get tomorrow off.
And then, hey, fondue date night.
That'll be fun.
Do.
Yeah, you know,
I was thinking maybe fondue date night
would be a good idea right now.
Really?
Everybody else is excited about it.
Even Ray.
What do you even bother with him?
I know he doesn't like to open up,
but little by little,
I think I'm cracking his shell.
You know what?
There's a sweet person inside.
Oh, listen.
I know you and Raymond have had your problems.
You can't talk too much.
What?
He called you Lady Blabbermouth.
He did?
Look, Amy, I'm sorry.
I've known Raymond for a long time, and
do you know what a
gel-ass is?
Huh.
Now that I think about it,
while we were talking this afternoon,
he did excuse himself to go to the bathroom
like five times.
I thought he had a tummy problem.
It's not his tummy.
He has no soul.
So he just wanted me to go away?
That is kind of...
jerky.
I love you so much.
You know, this is good.
Tomorrow night, more cheese for us.
No, no.
Everybody's coming.
I'm just not going to let Ray's opinion affect me.
Okay, good, good.
Hey, you know what?
Don't even talk to him.
In fact, just stay quiet all night.
We won't even
give him a chance to think that way about you.
Huh?
Oh.
Robert,
when I was just telling
you my sweater story,
and you told me to...
Was that because you think I talk too much?
No, no.
That's because
Raymond brought it up.
You know, and I didn't want him to think that he was right.
Because, you know, like you said,
jerky.
And I love this new sweater.
It's a great sweater.
Great story about the sweater.
I'm stealing that story!
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Amy, Amy, wait, wait.
Amy!
The one time I get a word in.
Okay, we have two different kinds of cheeses,
and the chocolate is for all the fruit.
Move it, lady, I'm going in.
Hello!
Oh, hi!
Oh, Amy, everything smells great.
That's what I said.
Marie, here is the garlic
toast I made for dipping.
Oh, thank you.
Hey, Mary.
Listen,
I began about before.
Sorry.
Oh, you don't have to apologize to me.
Ray, can I talk to you for a second?
Hey.
Sup, sis?
Listen, Ray.
Robert told me about what happened yesterday,
and I just want to let you know that
you're right.
I should have realized you're just a guy,
and guys just want to relax
and watch TV, and I should have left you alone.
Amy, will you marry me?
You know, listen, Amy.
Oh, no, no, no, Ray. I don't want things to be weird
between us, so I'm sorry.
Well, me too.
Great.
Let's sit and eat.
Okay, all right.
I don't mind if I fondue.
I got a cheese one.
Wait a minute!
That's it?
It's fine, Robert.
Let me get this straight.
Raymond insults you,
but you get mad at me,
and then you apologize to him?
What are you, taking lessons from my mom?
Who I am?
My love?
What's going on?
I'll tell you what's going on.
Yesterday, poor Raymond had to watch a basketball game
while Amy dared to sit next to him,
and then the minute she leaves,
he tells me that she had the nerve to talk to him
about things that didn't interest him,
called her Boxy Chatterhead.
Why would you call Amy a Boxy Chatterhead?
It's Lady Chatterley.
It's from a book.
It's okay.
To be fair, Ray is a sports writer.
It's kind of like I was bothering him at work.
Oh, Amy, no.
No, Ray doesn't work.
Apologize to Amy right now.
Excuse me.
This is between me and Amy,
and we're fine with it.
Amy, kudos on the fondue.
This is not between you and Amy.
What, are you kidding me?
You never listen, ever.
Never ever?
Oh, don't try to lay it all on Ray, Robert.
Last night, you made it very clear
that you think I talk too much.
Oh, dude.
You're the one who should be in trouble.
Yeah, Ray.
I know I think it,
but this chocolate and salami is a great combo.
All right, let's all just relax.
I think we're making too big a deal of this.
Oh, no, Amy, I have been putting up with this
for 15 years.
I am not gonna let him do this to you, too.
You know, when I need to talk to Ray
about, like, my feelings or our children,
I know I have until the commercial's over.
That gives me 30 seconds.
And if there's a girl in the commercial
who wants big wheels
or, God forbid, a monkey,
forget it.
Come on, it's not true.
Look, Ray, we're not asking for that much.
It's just talking and listening.
Watch. Hello, Robert.
Oh, hello there, Deborah. How's it going?
Not so good. I've got a brother
who lacks even rudimentary social skills.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Well, thanks for asking.
I'll take my earrings.
Yeah.
Oh, that was very good.
Raymond, do it with me now.
Hello, Raymond.
Hello, Mother.
Oh, look, Mom, a bear in pants.
Yes, your brother is quite hairy.
No, Ma, he's not doing it right.
Yes, yes, he is, Ma.
He's also ugly.
He should really wear a welder's mask.
Why don't I weld your mouth to your ass
and make a donut out of you?
You don't even know how to weld.
I'm a damn fine welder.
Oh, you're stinking everywhere.
I'm gonna weld the couch for you.
This is nothing to fight about.
Ray, just apologize to Amy.
No, it's okay.
We already talked about it.
And now it just seems like everybody's using it
as an excuse to attack him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
These jackals, they pounce as soon as they smell blood.
They love it when I'm miserable.
I know you guys have been sending her in
every day on purpose just to annoy me.
Amy.
Even I know you gotta go in there.
Yeah.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Just having some cookies.
Listen, uh,
I didn't mean what I said in there, really.
I was just, you know, I'm mad at those guys.
And I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Listen, you definitely have a right to be mad at me.
Oh, I do?
I do?
Well, thank you very much, Ray.
You're welcome.
Let me tell you something, mister.
You are a frustrating person.
All this time I've been trying to talk to you
and it's like I'm banging my head against the wall.
And I keep thinking, what's wrong with me?
Why can't I get through to him?
And now I realize that maybe it's not my fault.
Maybe it's just that you're boring.
You know,
Debra says you're like this because you don't want to talk.
But I think maybe it's because
you've got nothing to say.
I do, too, have stuff to say.
Oh, yeah? Go ahead.
Come on, talk.
Come on, talk. Right now.
And I want something more than hot dogs
and football kicking.
Yeah, oh!
Interesting conversation.
What else do you have to say, Mr. Fascinating?
This is a lot of pressure!
That's what I thought.
I'm sorry.
I was just lashing out.
Oh, I stink at this.
I was just trying to hurt your feelings.
Good job.
You want a tissue?
I'm not crying.
Look, Ray,
I know
I try too hard
talking about emotions and stuff.
It's just that
I want to be close to everyone in this family.
Why?
Because I love you guys.
But, I mean, for gosh
sakes, I know Frank better than I know you.
All his sights
and sounds and smells.
But at least I know he's comfortable with me.
I feel closer to him now.
Yeah, don't get
too close.
We lost the canary once.
You're always so funny.
You know what?
It's taken some time.
Even Robert has started opening up to me.
Like, he finally told me why he sleeps
with a tennis racket under his bed.
He still does that?
For the burglars.
That's what he told you
it's for? No, no, no, no, no.
That's...
That's his ghost swatter.
What? Yes, yes, yeah.
Ever since we were kids, he would...
Listen to this. One time,
he was about 12, and he thought he heard something in the attic.
And so, of course, I'm making fun of him.
So, to prove that he's not scared,
he went up there with his ghost swatter.
So I took a broom, and I went
boom, boom, boom, and all of a sudden,
two giant legs come crashing through the ceiling.
Boom!
Just his legs? Yeah, well, he fell on a beam.
It was just two giant legs just sticking out,
but they were still trying to run.
Was he injured?
Well, you tell me.
Yeah.
Hey, Amy, is, uh,
everything okay? Yeah.
Everything's fine, Robert. Amy and I,
we were just talking.
Yeah, we were. Uh-huh.
Oh, great. Well, that's very nice.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, please, by all means,
don't let me interrupt.
Okay.
Why aren't you talking?
What were you talking about?
Well, nothing. Shut up, really.
What were you talking about, Amy?
Under date night.
Was this about me?
What did you tell him?
You told him stuff about me. What did you say?
Nothing, Robert. He got stuff out of you.
I know him. Robert, we were just...
Hey, come on, Amy, we should get in there.
Dad's probably got the fondue pot on his head
like Winnie the Pooh.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Don't lie to me.
Is this about how I eat my foods
in alphabetical order? Because I have a very good reason
for that. I didn't know you'd
do that. I don't!
Amy, I don't want you talking
to him. Did you tell him about my pedicures?
No, Robert.
I didn't.
Robert paints his feet
like a lady!
Holy crap!
This commercial's funny.
Right, watch. Watch what the cat does.
He high-fives the dog.
That's funny. Those two don't usually get along.
Why don't you just sleep with him already?
I've been sitting here
all night too, you know.
Oh, look, this one's
got a monkey in it.
.