Hey, good morning.
Hey.
When did you finally come to bed?
Because I thought you were coming right up,
but then I fell asleep.
Yeah, the game.
We went into double overtime.
It was amazing.
Oh.
Because I thought we had plans.
Sorry.
God.
Did you catch the end of that game?
Oh, it was amazing.
See?
All right.
Well, I'll let you boys talk about your exciting sports.
I just hope there's not a game on tonight.
Huh.
What?
I think she just gave me the look.
What do you mean?
You know.
Sex.
That face means sex?
I thought it meant gas.
Oh.
Yeah.
I think Amy's in the mood now.
She does it better.
OK?
Yeah.
I know when Amy's in the mood.
Cause she always gives me this sexy little sideways smile.
Yeah.
I think Amy's saying hurry up and get it over with.
Mm-hmm.
Your mother's got a look, too.
Which is why after sunset, I avoid all eye contact.
Oh.
it's weird though it's weird okay last night i got the look but i i got caught up in the game
so i stayed up to watch instead of going upstairs and now instead of being mad deborah gave me the
look again huh maybe maybe i should turn her down again you know why would you do a silly thing
like that i don't know i mean i'm always the one being shot down it felt good her wondering where
i was last night you can't turn her down i could turn her down oh come on you'll follow her around
like a dog with his tongue hanging out yeah your tongue is the leash she uses to parade you around
the park ladies and gentlemen worst in show yeah well then uh maybe that's why i should turn her
down so she doesn't take me for granted you know
oh i mean she's got to appreciate what she's got here yes you're quite a catch
i can hardly keep my hands off you
hey
oh i left the hallway light on
i'll be right back
i can say no i can say no
you already asleep
you must be tired oh yeah i'm kind of beat you know i just i got a lot of stuff
going on
maybe tomorrow
really
yeah
okay
well night yeah good night
wait man come on let's go uh i don't think i'm gonna go hit balls today
what what oh why did the wife say you can't go no no it's just uh just a little stiff that's all
oh
so it's a medical decision you're making to stay here and helping me pick our drapes
ah drapes yeah
well there's any material left over once you make yourself a little skirt
i'm still gonna go and you know what i may go tomorrow because i can do whatever i want
what do you mean
all right
All right. You thought I couldn't turn down Debra, right?
Two times, my friend!
Yeah, last night I told her that I had a lot of work to do today.
Ha-ha-ha, work!
And then, and then, first thing this morning,
she started hinting again.
She even brushed her teeth and everything.
But no sale!
Oh, it's amazing. It's like, it's like,
every time I turn her down, she seems to want it more.
She's like a guy.
Huh. And she's not getting upset?
No, no, no, that's just it.
She's been treating me better all day.
I came down this morning, she was making me a cheese omelet.
I mean, she hasn't done that since before Allie was born.
I mean, yeah, it had shells in it, but still.
You know what I've discovered?
The power of no.
Oh, the power of no. Give me a break.
Hey, hey, hey, who gets to hit a bucket of balls
in the middle of the day?
Yeah, well, that's just the difference
between me and you, Raymond.
You know, you like to golf,
play yourself, and have a crappy omelet
while I prefer sex.
No, man, you're not getting it.
Deborah can't keep her hands off me.
It's like with the power of no
comes the power of yes.
Uh-huh.
For the first time in my marriage,
I finally know what it's like
to be the one wearing the panties.
You have a wrong and generally troubled relationship.
No, no, no, no, no, no, I don't.
It's very right.
But let me ask you something.
Why do you always feel the need
to be manipulative when it comes to sex?
Because I'm not very good at it.
Not very good at what?
Oh, you name it.
Hey, listen, Robert, he can't go hit balls,
but I was thinking that I'd still go.
Yeah, sure, go.
Have a good time.
All right.
Hey, you know what?
They got a great hot dog guy there.
You want me to bring you back one?
No, I shouldn't.
I got to watch my figure.
Hey, you let me be the one to watch your figure.
Let me watch your figure?
That's not funny.
That's right, it's not,
and yet it is!
Because she is weak.
Weak for my physique.
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
MUSIC PLAYS
MUSIC CONTINUES
MUSIC FADES
Oh, don't those look nice?
Yeah.
I don't know why Robert had such a hard time
putting them up yesterday.
Well, he can't handle normal-sized tools
with those giant fingers.
LAUGHTER
Here, push that curtain over a little
so we don't see his blood.
LAUGHTER
So, what do you think, Deb?
Yeah, they look great.
Deborah, dear,
you're being so quiet.
You're being so quiet.
quiet that's not like you I'm fine it's just do I look different to you what do
you mean I don't know I'm just feeling have I drooped you try to work out and
take care of yourself and there still comes a day when everything just I
wouldn't know about that you know how my friends and I keep fit water aerobics
at the Y say why don't you come with us tomorrow I'll have to check and see if
I'm free let me go look for an extra pair of nose clips and a swim cap
really upset about this keeps turning me down what do you mean sex that doesn't
sound like him he usually follows you around with his tongue hanging I'm sure
it's not you hey maybe he's sick
I wish he was oh man who am I kidding I should just go with Marie to the Y put on
a flowery swim cap and float around with the old ladies hey you know it's funny you
bringing this up because last night when Robert and I went to bed he was acting kind of distant
too but then I just kissed his neck and he said Ray's crazy he did yeah and then he said something
that was funny about the fact that you're a man but you're a woman and you're married
to a woman who you can't have a large body and you could have all the power
just weird yeah he usually doesn't like to mention Ray in the bedroom
says it inhibits him power I mean why
would he say oh my god oh my god he has been turning me down on purpose oh no
why would he do that?
For the power!
He thinks it gives him the upper hand or something.
Well, that's gross.
Hey, but look on the bright side.
This means you're still hot.
Of course I am.
You know what the worst part about this is?
That it worked.
I've been trying to make myself look better for him.
Do you know I did 138 sit-ups this morning
all for some guy whose stomach
looks like a deflated clown balloon.
Oh, boy, you're going to kill him, aren't you?
No.
No, I want him alive.
Hey, Jimmy Jack.
Hey.
How was work?
Good.
Where are the kids?
I sent them over to the Parker's.
Why?
I wanted them out of the house.
Oh, yeah?
I didn't think it would be appropriate
for the children to see what I was going to do to you.
Oh, gosh.
Really, Deb?
Right now, I don't know.
I mean, I got a lot to do.
Really, Deb, I think...
You're just so powerful.
Yeah, yeah, well...
I just can't resist a man with so much power.
Okay, look, I'm really starting to feel a little uncomfortable.
Ah!
What's with you?
Robert told Amy why you've been turning me down.
I hate that guy.
So you were just toying with me?
Getting me to beg for sex?
That makes you feel good?
No.
No, I don't know.
I just...
I guess I wanted to see what it was like
to be the one being pursued for once.
But you made me feel terrible about myself.
You just kept rejecting me.
How could you do that to somebody?
What?
You had me convinced I was a fat, ugly old lady.
Well, now you know how I feel.
You feel bad because I turned you down, what, three times?
Try being rejected 40 or 50 times every year
for the last 10 years.
How do you think that feels?
You're looking at the president
of the fat, ugly old ladies club.
Welcome.
Have a donut.
There is no way I turn you down that much.
And I say yes a lot.
Exactly.
You say yes and you say no.
You're the bouncer in front of the disco
who decides who gets in and who doesn't.
And for once it was you standing outside.
Yeah, and you couldn't take it.
Yeah, it's cold out there, isn't it?
Standing in the rain with your bad shirt
and your acne pimples.
There is no way you can compare me turning you down
with what you did to me.
Listen, Ray, if I turn you down,
it is because I am exhausted
from taking care of three kids all day
and thinking of everything that I have to do
the next day.
Still using the kids, huh?
Oh, my God.
I can't believe I ever wanted to have sex with you.
Yeah, well, you don't have to worry
because I'm not sure the next time
you're getting sex from me.
Oh, you're threatening me with no sex, please.
Yeah, you will be saying please.
Pretty please with sugar on top.
I'm serious.
I don't know when I'll be in the mood again.
You are always in the mood.
You wouldn't last.
You wouldn't last a night.
I just did three nights, Lady Pantaloons.
Okay, so we'll see who can't last.
Oh, my.
How will I ever resist my baser instincts?
Yeah.
I like that.
I like the Southern thing.
That'll be good when you come back saying
pretty please with sugar on top.
Finally.
Okay, well, good kno...
Ugh.
Oh!
oh my god are those silk I believe they're satin you want to feel quite
all right what's with all your lacy apparel nothing it's just pajamas
good night yeah yeah yeah I'm a little tired too
did you put oil on no it's just my natural juices
what are you doing maybe would you have my mom put your makeup on sex for you no sex for you
you
All right, you win!
What?
I give up!
I am officially asking you to please have some sex with me.
What are you talking about?
Our thing! Our not-having-sex thing!
Are we still doing that?
Of course we're still doing it.
It's been 26 days of doing it.
Not doing it!
Sorry, I totally forgot.
Yeah, right.
I mean, I can't believe it, but really, I totally forgot.
Please!
You expect me to believe that you didn't realize
that we went 26 days without having sex?
I've been really busy, you know.
The PTA fundraiser is coming up,