Ha!
Hi, Ray!
Oh, hey.
Oh, uh, Deb's not here.
She's out with the kids, so I'm just, you know,
trying to make the best of it.
Yeah.
Come.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I'm just gonna watch the Nick game, you know,
and, uh, nothing else.
Great.
Yeah, Robert called and told me you guys were gonna
watch the game when he got home from work, so I thought
I'd wait for him over here. Is that okay?
Oh, yeah, sure. Yeah.
All right.
So, so, uh, when did Robert say
he was gonna come home?
An hour.
Are you excited
about fondue date night?
Yeah.
What, what, what, what?
You guys are coming over tomorrow night
for Amy's first annual fondue night.
It's gonna be just the three of our own couples.
Like a triple date.
Hey.
Yeah, a date with my parents.
I know you think it's corny,
but it'll be fun. Really.
Fondue date night.
Yeah.
Yeah, fun.
Talk to Robert about it
when he gets here in, uh, 58 minutes.
May I?
Oh. Oh, yeah.
Oh, look.
This one looks like a heart.
So from now on,
that's where I'm buying all my sweaters.
Hey.
Hey, there he is.
There he is.
Hi, sweetie.
Missed you.
Yeah, what's up?
We've been waiting an hour and 11 minutes.
Uh, Amy, Ma wanted me to remind you
that you'll be making the salad for the dinner tonight.
Oh, I forgot.
I better go. Darn.
Yeah, damn it.
See you later, Yogi.
And, Ray, I'll see you at fondue.
Oh.
Okay, yeah.
This is such a cutie pie.
Yeah.
Oh, it's the second half already?
Yeah, man, you're missing some great basketball.
Yeah.
Actually, I kind of missed some, too.
I was, uh...
Me and Amy, we had a nice, long...
chat.
All right.
That's really nice. What did you guys talk about?
Oh, gosh, pretty much everything, I think.
Yeah.
Uh, Amy's great, huh?
Yeah, Amy's great. She's great.
Yeah.
She's kind of like a little Lady Chatterley.
Lady Chatterley?
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Oh, you know, like, she always wants to know
who everybody is, and she gets real excited
about fondue date night.
And she told me about
this interesting sales girl that sold her a sweater.
And, you know, whatever.
It's all good stuff.
It's all good.
Are you saying that Amy talks too much?
No, Robert, I love Amy.
Wow, are you a liar.
You know, I know what it is.
I got something good, and you can't stand it.
Oh, you never could.
Remember when I made that diorama
in Mr. Carolyn's history class?
What?
Everybody said how great it was.
Everybody!
I won a prize, remember?
But you said it stunk.
You had George Washington fighting a dinosaur.
It was a dragon, Raymond!
A dragon
that represented years
of British tyranny!
Which just goes to show
how stupid you were then and now.
Robert, I didn't...
Everybody thinks my wife is great.
Everybody!
So you have to tell me
that she's a lady chatterbox
who won't shut up?
I know how it goes.
Jealous ass.
Jealous!
Yes!
Stop it, no!
Come on, don't go, Robert, stay!
Stay and watch the game!
You want to say something bad
about my wife, you can.
I don't care.
Ah, come on!
Say it, say it!
She's a bad cook and she's mean!
Hey,
one second, one second.
And you may think that, Robert,
but you'll be dead wrong!
Dead wrong!
Deborah is a caring, beautiful,
skinny person.
So how's it going?
Look, I saved you this chip.
It looks like a heart.
Bye, honey!
I've been quiet all night.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Everything okay with you?
Fine and dandy.
Oh, did I show you this sweater I got?
It's nice.
The sales girl I bought it from, Bridget,
she was so sweet and smart.
She's taking some time off of school
to make some money,
but I really hope she finishes
because she was really great.
And then you bought the sweater.
Got it, got it.
I'm sorry.
Actually, you know,
I kind of did have a bad day.
Oh? What happened?
Oh, nothing.
It's just like every other day,
dealing with the scum of the earth.
Well,
at least you get tomorrow off.
And then, hey,
fondue date night.
That'll be fun.
Do.
Yeah, you know,
I was thinking,
maybe fondue date night
is not such a good idea right now.
Really?
Everybody else is excited about it,
even Ray.
Why do you even bother with him?
I know he doesn't like to open up,
but little by little,
I think I'm cracking his shell.
You know what?
There's a sweet person inside.
Oh, listen,
I know you and Raymond
have had your problems.
He said you talk too much.
What?
He called you Lady Blabbermouth.
He did?
Look, Amy, I'm sorry.
I've known Raymond
for a long time,
and do you know
he's got a lot of
Huh.
Now that I think about it,
while we were talking this afternoon,
he did excuse himself to go to the bathroom
like five times.
I thought he had a tummy problem.
It's not his tummy.
He has no soul.
So he just wanted me to go away?
That is kinda...
jerky.
I love you so much.
You know, this is good.
Tomorrow night, more cheese for us.
No, no, everybody's coming.
I'm just not gonna let Ray's
opinion affect me.
Okay, good, good.
Hey, you know what?
Don't even talk to him.
In fact, just stay quiet all night.
We won't even give him a chance
to think that way about you.
Huh?
Robert,
when I was just telling you
my sweater story,
and you told me to...
Was that because
you think I talk too much?
No, no.
That's because Raymond
brought it up, you know,
and I didn't want him to think that he was right.
Because, you know, like you said,
jerky.
And I love this new sweater.
It's a great sweater.
Great story about the sweater.
I'm stealing that story!
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Amy, Amy, wait, wait.
Amy!
The one time I get a word in.
Okay, we have
two different kinds of cheeses,
and the chocolate is for all the fruit.
Move it, lady, I'm going in.
Hello!
Oh, hi!
Oh, Amy, everything smells great.
That's what I said.
Marie, here is the garlic toast
I made for dipping.
Oh, thank you.
Hey, Ray.
Listen,
I began about before.
I'm sorry.
Oh, you don't have to apologize to me.
Ray, can I talk to you for a second?
.
What's up, sis?
Listen, Ray.
Robert told me about what happened yesterday,
and I just want to let you know that
you're right.
I should have realized you're just a guy,
and guys just want to relax
and watch TV, and I should have left you alone.
Amy, will you marry me?
You know, listen, Amy...
Oh, no, no, no, Ray.
I don't want things to be weird between us,
so I'm sorry.
Well,
me too.
Great. Let's sit and eat.
Okay, all right.
I don't mind if I fondue.
.
All right.
I got a cheese one.
Wait a minute!
.
That's it?
It's fine, Robert.
Let me get this straight.
Raymond insults you, but you get mad at me,
and then you apologize to him?
What, are you taking lessons from my mom?
.
Who I love?
What's going on?
Yesterday, poor Raymond had to watch a basketball game
while Amy dared to sit next to him,
and then the minute she leaves,
he tells me that she had the nerve to talk to him
about things that didn't interest him,
called her Boxy Chatterhead.
.
Why would you call Amy
a Boxy Chatterhead?
It's Lady Chatterley.
It's from a book.
Oh, no, it's okay.
To be fair, Ray is a sports writer.
It's kind of like I was bothering him at work.
Oh, Amy.
No.
No, Ray doesn't work.
Apologize to Amy right now.
Excuse me, this is between me and Amy,
and we're fine with it.
Amy, kudos on the fondue.
.
This is not between you and Amy.
What, are you kidding me?
You never listen, ever.
Never ever.
Oh, don't try to lay it all on Ray, Robert.
Last night you made it very clear
that you think I talk too much.
Oh, dude.
You're the one who should be in trouble.
Yeah, Ray.
You know, you wouldn't think it,
but this chocolate and salami is a great combo.
All right, let's all just relax.
I think we're making too big a deal of this.
Oh, no, Amy.
I've been hanging up with this for 15 years.
I am not gonna let him do this to you, too.
You know, when I need to talk to Ray
about, like, my feelings or our children,
I know I have until the commercial's over.
That gives me 30 seconds.
And if there's a girl in the commercial
or a truck with big wheels
or, God forbid, a monkey,
forget it.
Come on, it's not true.
Look, Ray, we're not asking for that much.
It's just talking and listening.
Watch. Hello, Robert.
Oh, hello there, Debra.
How's it going?
Not so good. I've got a brother who lacks
even rudimentary social skills.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Well, thanks for asking.
And by the way, those are lovely earrings.
Yeah.
Oh, that was very good.
Raymond, do it with me now.
Hello, Raymond.
Hello, Mother.
Oh, look, Mom, a bear in pants.
Yes, your brother is quite hairy.
No, Ma, he's not doing it right.
Yes, yes, he is.
Ma, he's also ugly.
He should really wear a welder's mask.
Why don't I weld your mouth to your ass
and make a doughnut out of you?
You don't even know how to weld.
I'm a damn fine welder.
Oh, you're stinking every day.
I'm gonna weld the couch for you.
This is nothing to fight about.
Ray, just apologize to Amy.
No, it's okay.
We already talked about it.
And now it just seems like everybody's using it
as an excuse to attack him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
These jackals, they pounce as soon as they smell blood.
They love it when I'm miserable.
For all I know, you guys have been sending her in
every day on purpose just to annoy me.
Oh, Amy.
Oh.
Even I know you gotta go in there.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Just having some cookies.
Listen, uh, I didn't mean what I said in there, really.
I was just, you know, I'm mad at those guys.
And I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm fine.
Listen, you definitely have a right to be mad at me.
Oh, I do?
I do?
Well, thank you very much, Ray.
You're welcome.
Let me tell you something, mister.
You are a frustrating person.
All this time I've been trying to talk to you
and it's like I'm banging my head against the wall.
And I keep thinking, what's wrong with me?
Why can't I get through to him?
And now I realize that maybe it's not my fault.
Maybe it's just that you're boring.
You know,
Debra says you're like this because you don't want to talk.
But I think maybe it's because
you've got nothing to say.
I do, too, have stuff to say.
Oh, yeah? Go ahead.
Come on, talk.
Come on, talk. Right now.
And I want something more than hot dogs
and football kicking.
I just...
Oh, interesting conversation.
What else do you have to say, Mr. Fascinating?
This is a lot of pressure!
That's what I thought.
I'm sorry.
I was just lashing out.
Oh, I stink at this.
I was just trying to hurt your feelings.
Good job.
Do you want a tissue?
I'm not crying.
Look, Ray,
I know I try too hard
talking about emotions
and stuff.
But I want to be close
to everyone in this family.
Why?
Because I love you guys.
But, I mean, for gosh sakes,
I know Frank better than I know you.
All his sights and sounds
and smells.
But at least I know
he's comfortable with me.
I feel closer to him now.
Yeah, don't get too close.
We lost a canary once.
You're always so funny.
You know what?
It's taken some time.
But even Robert has started opening up to me.
Like, he finally told me
why he sleeps with a tennis racket under his bed.
He still does that?
For the burglars.
That's what he told you it's for?
No, no, no, no, no.
That's...
That's his ghost swatter.
What?
Yes, yes, yeah.
Ever since we were kids,
he would...
Listen to this.
One time, he was about 12,
and he thought he heard something in the attic.
And so, of course, I'm making fun of him.
So to prove that he's not scared,
he went up there with his ghost swatter.
So I took a broom, and I went boom, boom, boom.
And all of a sudden,
two giant legs come crashing through the ceiling.
Boom! Just his legs?
Ah!
It was just two giant legs
just sticking there,
but they were still trying to run.
Ah!
Was he injured?
Well, you tell me.
Hey, Amy, is everything okay?
Yeah. Everything's fine, Robert.
Amy and I, we were just talking.
Yeah, we were.
Uh-huh.
Oh, great. Well, that's very nice.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, please, by all means,
don't let me interrupt.
Uh...
Why aren't you talking?
What were you talking about?
Well, nothing. Shut up, really.
What were you talking about, Amy?
Under date night.
Oh.
Was this about me?
What did you tell him?
You told him stuff about me. What did you say?
Nothing, Robert.
He got stuff out of you. I know him.
Robert, we were just...
Hey, come on, Amy, we should get in there.
Dad's probably got the fondue pot on his head
like Winnie the Pooh.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Don't lie to me.
Is this about how I eat my foods in alphabetical order?
Because I have a very good reason for that.
I didn't know you'd do that.
I don't!
Amy, I don't want you talking to him.
Did you tell him about my pedicures?
No, Robert.
Robert paints his feet like a lady!
Holy crap!
You're such a jerk!
This commercial's funny.
Right, watch. Watch what the cat does.
Oh, he high-fives the dog.
That's funny.
Those two don't usually get along.
Why don't you just sleep with him already?
Oh, my God!
That's funny.
I've been sitting here all night, too, you know.
Oh, look, this one's got a monkey in it.
You're such a jerk.
Oh, you're such a jerk.
Oh, God!
Well, well, well.