Ha!
Hi, Ray!
Oh, hey.
Oh, uh, Deb's not here.
She's out with the kids, so I'm just, you know,
trying to make the best of it.
Yeah.
Come.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I'm just gonna watch the Nick game, you know,
and, uh, nothing else.
Great.
Yeah, Robert called and told me you guys were gonna
watch the game when he got home from work, so I thought
I'd wait for him over here. Is that okay?
Oh, yeah, sure. Yeah.
All right.
So, so, uh, when did Robert say
he was gonna come home?
An hour.
Are you excited
about fondue date night?
Yeah.
What, what, what, what?
You guys are coming over tomorrow night
for Amy's first annual fondue night.
It's gonna be just the three of our own couples.
Like a triple date.
Hey.
Yeah, a date with my parents.
I know you think it's corny,
but it'll be fun. Really.
Fondue date night.
Yeah.
Yeah, fun.
Talk to Robert about it
when he gets here in, uh, 58 minutes.
May I?
Oh. Oh, yeah.
Oh, look.
This one looks like a heart.
So from now on,
that's where I'm buying all my sweaters.
Hey.
Hey, there he is.
There he is.
Hi, sweetie.
Missed you.
Yeah, what's up?
We've been waiting an hour and 11 minutes.
Uh, Amy, Ma wanted me to remind you
that you'll be making the salad for the dinner tonight.
Oh, I forgot.
I better go. Darn.
Yeah, damn it.
See you later, Yogi.
And, Ray, I'll see you at fondue.
Oh.
Okay, yeah.
This is such a cutie pie.
Yeah.
Oh, it's the second half already?
Yeah, man, you're missing some great basketball.
Yeah.
Actually, I kind of missed some, too.
I was, uh...
Me and Amy, we had a nice, long...
chat.
All right.
That's really nice. What did you guys talk about?
Oh, gosh, pretty much everything, I think.
Yeah.
Uh, Amy's great, huh?
Yeah, Amy's great. She's great.
Yeah.
She's kind of like a little Lady Chatterley.
Lady Chatterley?
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Oh, you know, like, she always wants to know
who everybody is, and she gets real excited
about fondue date night.
And she told me about
this interesting sales girl that sold her a sweater.
And, you know, whatever.
It's all good stuff.
It's all good.
Are you saying that Amy talks too much?
No, Robert, I love Amy.
Wow, are you a liar.
You know, I know what it is.
I got something good, and you can't stand it.
Oh, you never could.
Remember when I made that diorama
in Mr. Carolyn's history class?
What?
Everybody said how great it was.
Everybody!
I won a prize, remember?
But you said it stunk.
You had George Washington fighting a dinosaur.
It was a dragon, Raymond!
A dragon
that represented years
of British tyranny!
Which just goes to show
how stupid you were then and now.
Robert, I didn't...
Everybody thinks my wife is great.
Everybody!
So you have to tell me
that she's a lady chatterbox
who won't shut up?
I know how it goes.
Jealous ass.
Jealous!
Yes!
Stop it, no!
Come on, don't go, Robert, stay!
Stay and watch the game!
You want to say something bad
about my wife, you can.
I don't care.
Ah, come on!
Say it, say it!
She's a bad cook and she's mean!
Hey,
one second, one second.
And you may think that, Robert,
but you'll be dead wrong!
Dead wrong!
Deborah is a caring, beautiful,
skinny person.