- Hey, good mornin'.
- Hey.
When did you
finally come to bed?
'Cause I thought
you were coming right up,
but then I fell asleep.
- Yeah, the game,
it went into double overtime.
It was amazing.
- Oh...
'Cause I thought
we had plans.
- Sorry. God...
- Did you catch
the end of that game?
- Oh, it was amazing.
- See?
- All right.
Well, I'll let you boys
talk about your exciting sports.
I just hope there's
not a game on tonight.
- Huh.
- What?
- I think she just
gave me the look.
- What do you mean?
- You know...
Sex.
- That face means "sex"?
I thought it meant "gas."
- She does it better, okay?
- Yeah, I know
when Amy's in the mood,
'cause she always gives me
this sexy little sideways smile.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I think Amy's saying,
"hurry up
and get it over with."
- Your mother's
got a look, too,
which is why after sunset,
I avoid all eye contact.
- It's weird, though.
It's weird.
Okay, last night,
I got the look.
But I got caught up
in the game,
so I stayed up to watch it
instead of going upstairs.
And now,
instead of being mad,
Debra gave me
the look again.
Huh.
- Maybe--maybe I should
turn her down again,
you know?
- Why would you do
a silly thing like that?
- I don't know.
I mean, I'm always
the one being shot down.
It felt good, her wondering
where I was last night.
- You can't turn her down.
- I-I could too
turn her down.
- Oh, come on,
you follow her around
like a dog with
his tongue hanging out.
- Yeah, your tongue
is the leash she uses
to parade you
around the park.
[Laughing]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
worst in show!
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, well, then maybe
that's why I should
turn her down.
So she doesn't
take me for granted.
You know? I mean, she's got to
appreciate what she's got here.
- Yes, you're quite a catch.
I can hardly
keep my hands off you.
Come on, come on!
- Stupid.
- Hey.
- Oh,
I left the hallway light on.
I'll be right back.
I can say "no."
I can say
"no."
- You already asleep?
- Huh? What?
- You must be tired.
- Oh, yeah,
I am kind of beat.
You know, I just--
I got a lot of...
Stuff...
...going on.
Maybe tomorrow.
- Really?
- Yeah...
- Okay.
Well, night.
- Yeah.
[Yawns]
Good night.
Where were you, man?
Come on, let's go!
- Ah, I don't think I'm gonna
go hit balls today.
- What--what?
Oh, what, did the wife
say you can't go?
- No, no, just a little
stiff, that's all.
- Oh, so it's
a medical decision
you're making
to stay here and...
- Help Amy pick out drapes.
- [Chuckles]
Ah, drapes, yeah.
Well, if there's any
material left over,
why don't you make yourself
a little skirt?
I'm still gonna go,
and you know what?
I may go tomorrow, because
I can do whatever I want.
- What do you mean?
- All right, you thought I
couldn't turn down Debra, right?
Two times, my friend!
Yeah, last night,
I told her
that I had a lot
of work to do today.
[Scoffs]
Work!
And then--and then,
first thing this morning,
she started hinting again.
She even brushed her teeth
and everything,
but no sale!