- Aha.
[Door opens]
- Hi, ray.
- Oh, hey.
- Oh, Deb's not here;
She's out with the kids,
so I'm just...You know,
trying to make the best of it.
- Yeah.
- Oh...oh, okay.
Yeah, I'm just gonna
watch the knick game,
you know, and...
Nothing else.
- Great; Yeah, Robert called
and told me
you guys were gonna
watch the game
when he got home from work,
so I thought I'd wait
for him over here.
Is that okay?
- Oh, yeah, sure. Yeah.
So when did Robert say
he was gonna come home?
- About an hour.
Are you excited about
fondue date night?
- What--what--what what?
- You guys are coming over
tomorrow night
for Amy's first annual
fondue night.
It's gonna be just
the three barone couples,
like a triple date.
- Hey...
Hey, a date with my parents.
- I know you think it's corny,
but it'll be fun, really.
Fondue date night.
- Yeah.
Yeah, fun.
You know what?
I'll talk to Robert about it
when he gets here
in 58 minutes.
- Oh, may I?
- Oh. Oh, yeah.
- Thanks.
Oh, look, this one
looks like a heart.
So from now on,
that's where I'm buying
all my sweaters.
- Hey!
- Hey, hey, there he is!
There he is!
- Hi, sweetie.
- Hello, there.
- Missed you.
- Yeah, what's up?
We've been waiting
an hour and 11 minutes.
- Amy, ma wanted me
to remind you that
you'll be making the salad
for the dinner tonight.
- Oh, I forgot.
I better go.
Darn.
- Yeah, damn it.
- See you later, yogi.
And, ray, I'll see you
at fondue.
- Okay, yeah.
- She's such a cutie pie.
[Both groan]
Oh, it's
the second half already?
- Yeah, man, you're missing
some great basketball.
Actually, I kind of
missed some too.
I was--me and Amy,
we had a nice long...
Chat.
- All right,
that's really nice.
What did you guys
talk about?
- Oh, gosh, pretty much
everything, I think, yeah.
- Yeah, Amy's great, huh?
- Yeah, Amy's great.
She's great. Yeah.
Kind of like
a little lady chatterley.
- Lady chatterley?
- Yeah.
- What do you mean?
- Oh, you know,
like she always--
she always wants to know
how everybody is,
and she gets real excited
about fondue date night.
And she told me about
this interesting salesgirl
that sold her a sweater
and--and--and, you know,
whatever; It's all good stuff;
It's all good.
- Are you saying that
Amy talks too much?
- No, Robert, I love Amy.
- Wow, are you a liar.
You know,
I know what it is.
I got something good,
and you can't stand it.
You never could.
Remember when
I made that diorama
in Mr. Carolan's
history class?
- What?
- Everybody said
how great it was, everybody!
I won a prize, remember?
But you said it stunk.
- You had George Washington
fighting a dinosaur.
- It was a dragon, Raymond!
A dragon that represented
years of British tyranny!
Which just goes to show
how stupid you were
then and now.
- Robert, I didn't--
- everybody thinks
my wife is great.
Everybody!
So you have to tell me that
she's a lady chatterbox
who won't shut up?
I know how it goes.
Jealous ass.
- Come on--
- jeal-ass!
Yes!
- Stop it! No!
Come on, don't go, Robert!
Stay! Come stay
and watch the game!
Come on.
You want to say something bad
about my wife, you can!
I don't care!
Ah, come on!
Say it! Say it!
She's a bad cook,
and she's mean!
Hey, hi...One second,
one second.
And you may
think that, Robert.
You'd be dead wrong!
Dead wrong!
Debra is a caring,
beautiful, skinny person!