Hey, good morning.
Hey.
When did you finally come to bed?
Because I thought you were coming right up,
but then I fell asleep.
Yeah, the game.
We went into double overtime.
It was amazing.
Oh.
Because I thought we had plans.
Sorry.
God.
Did you catch the end of that game?
Oh, it was amazing.
See?
All right.
Well, I'll let you boys talk about your exciting sports.
I just hope there's not a game on tonight.
Huh.
What?
I think she just gave me the look.
What do you mean?
You know.
Sex.
That face means sex?
I thought it meant gas.
Oh.
it's weird though it's weird okay last night i got the look but i i got caught up in the game
so i stayed up to watch instead of going upstairs and now instead of being mad deborah gave me the
look again huh maybe maybe i should turn her down again you know why would you do a silly thing like
that i don't know i mean i'm always the one being shot down it felt good her wondering where i was
last night you can't turn her down i could turn her down oh come on you'll follow her around like
a dog with his tongue hanging out yeah your tongue is the leash she uses to parade you around the
park ladies and gentlemen worst in show yeah well then uh maybe that's why i should turn her down
so she doesn't take me for granted you know
i mean she's got to appreciate what she's got here yes you're quite a catch
i can hardly keep my hands off you
hey
oh i left the hallway light on
i'll be right back
i can say no i can say no
you
already asleep
uh-oh
you must be tired oh yeah i'm kind of beat you know i just i got a lot of stuff
going on
maybe tomorrow
really
yeah
okay
well night yeah oh good night
wait man come on let's go uh i don't think i'm gonna go hit balls today
what oh why did the wife say you can't go no no it's just uh just a little stiff that's all
oh
so it's a medical decision you're making to stay here and helping me pick out drapes
ah drapes yeah well there's any material left over once you make yourself a little skirt
i'm still gonna go and you know what i may go tomorrow because i can do whatever i want
what do you mean all right
you thought i couldn't turn down deborah right two times my friend
that's good
last night i told her that i had a lot of work to do today
work
and then and then first thing this morning she started hinting again
she even brushed your teeth and everything
no sale