- Hey, good mornin'.
- Hey.
When did you
finally come to bed?
'Cause I thought
you were coming right up,
but then I fell asleep.
- Yeah, the game,
it went into double overtime.
It was amazing.
- Oh...
'Cause I thought
we had plans.
- Sorry. God...
- Did you catch
the end of that game?
- Oh, it was amazing.
- See?
- All right.
Well, I'll let you boys
talk about your exciting sports.
I just hope there's
not a game on tonight.
- Huh.
- What?
- I think she just
gave me the look.
- What do you mean?
- You know...
Sex.
- That face means "sex"?
I thought it meant "gas."
- She does it better, okay?
- Yeah, I know
when Amy's in the mood,
'cause she always gives me
this sexy little sideways smile.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I think Amy's saying,
"hurry up
and get it over with."
- Your mother's
got a look, too,
which is why after sunset,
I avoid all eye contact.
- It's weird, though.
It's weird.
Okay, last night,
I got the look.
But I got caught up
in the game,
so I stayed up to watch it
instead of going upstairs.
And now,
instead of being mad,
Debra gave me
the look again.
Huh.
- Maybe--maybe I should
turn her down again,
you know?
- Why would you do
a silly thing like that?
- I don't know.
I mean, I'm always
the one being shot down.
It felt good, her wondering
where I was last night.
- You can't turn her down.
- I-I could too
turn her down.
- Oh, come on,
you follow her around
like a dog with
his tongue hanging out.
- Yeah, your tongue
is the leash she uses
to parade you
around the park.
[Laughing]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
worst in show!
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, well, then maybe
that's why I should
turn her down.
So she doesn't
take me for granted.
You know? I mean, she's got to
appreciate what she's got here.
- Yes, you're quite a catch.
I can hardly
keep my hands off you.
Come on, come on!
- Stupid.
- Hey.
- Oh,
I left the hallway light on.
I'll be right back.
I can say "no."
I can say
"no."
- You already asleep?
- Huh? What?
- You must be tired.
- Oh, yeah,
I am kind of beat.
You know, I just--
I got a lot of...
Stuff...
...going on.
Maybe tomorrow.
- Really?
- Yeah...
- Okay.
Well, night.
- Yeah.
[Yawns]
Good night.
Where were you, man?
Come on, let's go!
- Ah, I don't think I'm gonna
go hit balls today.
- What--what?
Oh, what, did the wife
say you can't go?
- No, no, just a little
stiff, that's all.
- Oh, so it's
a medical decision
you're making
to stay here and...
- Help Amy pick out drapes.
- [Chuckles]
Ah, drapes, yeah.
Well, if there's any
material left over,
why don't you make yourself
a little skirt?
I'm still gonna go,
and you know what?
I may go tomorrow, because
I can do whatever I want.
- What do you mean?
- All right, you thought I
couldn't turn down Debra, right?
Two times, my friend!
Yeah, last night,
I told her
that I had a lot
of work to do today.
[Scoffs]
Work!
And then--and then,
first thing this morning,
she started hinting again.
She even brushed her teeth
and everything,
but no sale!
Ah, it's amazing, it's like--
it's like every time
I turn her down,
she seems to want it more.
She's like a guy.
- Huh, and she's
not getting upset?
- No, no, no, that's just it.
She's been treating me
better all day.
I came in this morning, she
was making me a cheese omelet.
I mean, she hasn't done that
since before ally was born!
I mean, yeah,
it had shells in it, but still.
You know what
I've discovered?
The power of "no."
- "The power of 'no.'"
Give me a break.
- Hey, hey, hey, who gets to hit
a bucket of balls
in the middle of the day?
- Yeah, well,
that's just the difference
between me and you,
Raymond.
You like to golf by yourself
and have a crappy omelet,
while I prefer sex.
- No.
- Yes.
No, man,
you're not gettin' it.
Debra can't
keep her hands off me.
It's like with
the power of "no"
comes the power of "yes."
Uh-huh.
For the first time
in my marriage,
I finally know
what it's like
to be the one
wearin' the panties.
- You have a wrong and
generally troubled relationship.
- No, no, no, no,
no, I don't.
It's very right.
- Then let me ask you something.
Why do you always
feel the need
to be manipulative
when it comes to sex?
- Because...
I'm not very good at it.
- You're not very good
at what?
- Oh, you name it.
Hey, listen, Robert--
he can't go hit balls,
but I was thinkin'
that I'd still go.
- Yeah, sure, go.
Have a good time.
- All right.
Hey, you know what?
They got a great
hot dog guy there.
You want me
to bring you back one?
- No, I shouldn't.
I got to watch my figure.
- Hey, you let me be the one
to watch your figure.
- [Giggles]
- "Let me watch your figure"?
That's not funny.
- That's right, it's not,
and yet, it is!
Because she is weak.
Weak...for my physique.
[Clattering]
- Oh, don't those look nice?
- Yeah.
I don't know why Robert
had such a hard time
putting them up yesterday.
- Well, he can't handle
normal-sized tools
with those giant fingers.
Here, push that curtain over
a little
so we don't see his blood.
- So what do you think,
Deb?
- Yeah, they look great.
- Debra, dear.
You're being so quiet.
That's not like you.
- No, I'm fine, it's just--
do I look different
to you?
- What do you mean?
- I don't know,
I'm just feeling--
have I drooped?
- Drooped?
- You know, you try to work out
and take care of yourself,
and yet there still comes a day
when everything just...
[Mimics exploding sound]
- I wouldn't know about that.
- Oh, stop it, Deb.
You look great.
- You know how my friends
and I keep fit?
Water aerobics at the "y."
Say, why don't you
come with us tomorrow?
- Oh, wow, I'll have to check
and see if I'm free.
- Oh, we'll have a ball!
Let me go look
for an extra pair of nose clips
and a swim cap.
- Debra, you're really
upset about this.
- Ray keeps turning me down.
- What do you mean, sex?
- Yeah.
- That doesn't sound like him.
He usually follows you around
with his tongue hanging out.
- I know.
- Well, I'm sure it's not you.
Hey, maybe he's sick.
- Nah.
I wish he was.
Oh, man, who am I kidding?
I should just go
with Marie to the "y,"
put on a flowery swim cap,
and float around
with the old ladies.
- You know, it's funny,
you bringing this up,
because last night
when Robert and I went to bed,
he was acting
kind of distant too.
But then I just
kissed his neck, and he said,
"Ray's crazy."
- He did?
- Yeah, and then he said
something about
how I could have
all the power.
It was weird.
Yeah, he usually doesn't like
to mention ray in the bedroom.
He says it inhibits him.
- "The power"?
I mean, why would he say--
oh...
- What?
- Oh, my god.
Oh, my god!
He has been
turning me down on purpose!
- Oh, no,
why would he do that?
- For the power!
He thinks it gives him
the upper hand or something.
- Well, that's gross.
Hey, but look on
the bright side.
This means you're still hot.
- Of course I am.
You know what the worst part
about this is?
That it worked.
I've been trying to make myself
look better for him.
Do you know I did
138 sit ups this morning?
All for some guy
whose stomach
looks like a deflated
clown balloon!
- Oh, boy, you're gonna
kill him, aren't you?
- No.
No, I want him alive.
- Hey, jimmyjack.
- Hey.
How was work?
- Good. Where are the kids?
- I sent them over
to the Parkers.
- Why?
- I wanted them
out of the house.
- Oh, yeah?
- I didn't think
it would be appropriate
for the children to see
what I was going to do to you.
- Oh, gosh, really, Deb?
Right now? I don't know.
I mean, I got a lot to do.
Really, Deb, I think--
- [whispers]
You're just so powerful.
- Yeah, yeah, well--
- I just can't resist a man
with so much power.
- Okay, look, I'm really
starting to feel a little--
[screams]
What's with you?
- Robert told Amy
why you've been turning me down.
- I hate that guy!
- So you were
just toying with me,
getting me to beg for sex?
That makes you feel good?
- No, no, I don't know,
I just--
I guess I wanted
to see what it was like
to be the one
being pursued for once.
- But you made me feel
terrible about myself!
You just kept rejecting me.
How could you
do that to somebody?
- What?
- You had me convinced
I was a fat, ugly, old lady!
- Well,
now you know how I feel!
You feel bad because I turned
you down, what, three times?
Try being rejected
40 or 50 times every year
for the last 10 years!
How do you think that feels?
You're lookin'
at the president
of the fat, ugly,
old ladies club!
Welcome! Have a donut!
- There is no way
I turn you down that much.
And I say "yes" a lot.
- Exactly! You say yes,
and you say no.
You're the--you're the bouncer
in front of the disco
who decides who gets in
and who doesn't.
And for once,
it was you standin' outside.
Yeah,
and you couldn't take it.
it's cold out there, isn't it?
Standing in the rain,
with your bad shirt
and your acne pimples.
- There is no way you can
compare me turning you down
with what you did to me!
Listen, ray,
if I turn you down,
it is
because I am exhausted
from taking care
of three kids all day
and thinking of everything
that I have to do the next day.
- Still using the kids, huh?
- Oh, my god.
I can't believe I ever wanted
to have sex with you.
- Well, you don't have to worry,
because I'm not sure
the next time
you're getting sex from me.
- Oh, you're threatening me
with no sex?
Please.
- Yeah,
you will be saying please--
pretty please with sugar on top.
I'm serious.
I don't know when
I'll be in the mood again.
- You are always in the mood.
You wouldn't last a night.
- I just did three nights,
lady pantaloons.
Okay?
So we'll see who can't last.
- [Southern accent]
Oh, my.
How will I ever
resist my baser instincts?
- Yeah, I like that.
I like the southern thing.
That'll be good
when you come back saying,
[southern accent] "Pretty please
with sugar on top."
- Okay, well, good--
[groans]
Oh, my god,
are those silk?
- I believe they're satin.
You want to feel?
- That's quite all right.
- What's with
all your Lacy apparel?
- Nothing.
It's just pajamas.
Good night.
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah,
I'm a little tired too.
[Groans]
- Did you put oil on?
- No.
It's just my natural juices.
- What are you doing?
- Me?
What, did you have my mom
put your makeup on?
- No sex for you!
- No sex for you.
[Jazzy lounge music]
All right, you win!
- What?
- I give up!
I am officially
asking you
to please
have some sex with me.
- What are you talking about?
- Our thing.
Our not having sex thing.
- Are we still doing that?
- Of course
we're still doing it.
It's been 26 days
of doing it--
not doing it.
- I'm sorry.
I totally forgot.
- Yeah, right.
- I mean, I can't believe it,
but really,
I totally forgot.
- Please.
You expect me to believe that
you didn't realize that we--
we went 26 days
without having sex?
- It's just,
I've been really busy.
You know, the pta fund-raiser
is coming up,
and I've just had
a lot on my mind.
- 26 days.
You weren't even trying.
Guess I was never really close
to havin' the power, was I?
- Sorry.
- All this time,
I-I thought you were doin'
all those little things
to torture me.
- What things?
- Forget it.
- No, come on.
- You know.
Like bite your lower lip
when you use the remote
to change the channel.
- I do that?
- Yeah!
Or how about
when you keep one of your legs
outside of the covers
and the pajama rides up it?
- It's just because I'm hot.
- Yes, you are!
Even when you sleep,
every so often,
you kind of sigh a little.
[Sighs quietly]
- You haven't
slept much lately, have you?
- No.
Even now.
Look at you.
With your hair like that,
sittin' there in your...
Robe.
- I'm a mess.
- Yeah, well, I guess
even when you're not tryin',
it still works.
- What? What are you doin'?
- You just got
a little of your power back.
- [Laughs]
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
Are you toying with me?
Because if you are,
I'm just gonna
start to cry.
- I've been waiting for this
for a long time, too, ray.
And by the way,
it's been 27 days, not 26.
- Ah, you do re--
--member!
- [Laughs]
- Morning.
- Morning, kids.
- What are you doin' here?
- We live here.
- No, no, no, no, no!
Hey, you guys can
make breakfast yourself, right?
'Cause daddy has to talk to
mommy upstairs about something.
- Ray.
- Yeah?
[Mumbles weakly]