Because I thought you were coming right up,
Did you catch the end of that game?
Well, I'll let you boys talk about your
I just hope there's not a game on
I think she just gave me the look.
though it's weird okay last night i got
weird though it's weird okay last night i
it's weird though it's weird okay last night
it's weird okay last night i got the
but i i got caught up in the
so i stayed up to watch instead of
of going upstairs and now instead of being
instead of being mad deborah gave me the
look again huh maybe maybe i should turn
maybe i should turn her down again you
why would you do a silly thing like
that i don't know i mean i'm always
i mean i'm always the one being shot
it felt good her wondering where i was
last night you can't turn her down i
night you can't turn her down i could
down oh come on you'll follow her around
a dog with his tongue hanging out yeah
yeah your tongue is the leash she uses
the leash she uses to parade you around
park ladies and gentlemen worst in show yeah
worst in show yeah well then uh maybe
uh maybe that's why i should turn her
so she doesn't take me for granted you
i mean she's got to appreciate what she's
what she's got here yes you're quite a
i can hardly keep my hands off you
i can say no i can say no
you must be tired oh yeah i'm kind
yeah i'm kind of beat you know i
you know i just i got a lot
wait man come on let's go uh i
i don't think i'm gonna go hit balls
oh why did the wife say you can't
it's just uh just a little stiff that's
so it's a medical decision you're making to
a medical decision you're making to stay here
to stay here and helping me pick out
ah drapes yeah well there's any material left
left over once you make yourself a little
i'm still gonna go and you know what
may go tomorrow because i can do whatever
you thought i couldn't turn down deborah right
couldn't turn down deborah right two times my
last night i told her that i had
that i had a lot of work to
and then and then first thing this morning
then first thing this morning she started hinting
then and then first thing this morning she
oh it's amazing it's like it's like every
it's like it's like every time i turn
i turn it down she seems to want
oh it's amazing it's like it's like every
came down this morning, she was making me
this morning, she was making me a cheese
I mean, she hasn't done that since before
I mean, yeah, it had shells in it,
Oh, the power of no. Give me a
the power of no. Give me a break.
hey, who gets to hit a bucket of
Oh, the power of no. Give me a
You know, you like to golf by yourself
have a crappy omelet, while I prefer sex.
power of no comes the power of yes.
It's like with the power of no comes
No, no, no, no, no, no, I don't.
to be manipulative when it comes to sex?
Hey, listen, Robert, he can't go hit balls,
but I was thinking that I'd still go.
Hey, you let me be the one to
They got a great hot dog guy there.
You want me to bring you back one?
me be the one to watch your figure.
Hey, you let me be the one to
let me be the one to watch your
That's right, it's not, and yet it is.
I don't know why Robert had such a
You know how my friends and I keep
Say, why don't you come with us tomorrow?
I'll have to check and see if I'm
Oh, well, I'll have to check and see
Let me go look for an extra pair
He usually follows you around with his tongue
I should just go with Marie to the
because last night when Robert and I went
And then he said something about how I
about how I could have all the power.
Yeah, he usually doesn't like to mention Ray
And then he said something about how I
The power is in the upper hand or
power is in the upper hand or something.
You know, the worst part about this is
Do you know I did 138 sit ups
worst part about this is that it worked.
I've been trying to make myself look better
Do you know I did 138 sit ups
this morning all for some guy whose stomach
all for some guy whose stomach looks like
I didn't think it would be appropriate for
to see what I was going to do
I mean, I got a lot to do.
I just can't resist a man with so
Okay, look, I'm really starting to feel a
Robert told Amy why you've been turning me
to be the one being pursued for once.
But you made me feel terrible about myself.
I guess I wanted to see what it
guess I wanted to see what it was
to be the one being pursued for once.
But you made me feel terrible about myself.
I guess I wanted to see what it
You had me convinced I was a fat,
feel bad because I turned you down, what,
Try being rejected 40 or 50 times every
is no way I turn you down that
There is no way I turn you down
Exactly. You say yes, and you say no.
You're the bouncer in front of the disco
who decides who gets in and who doesn't.
And for once, it was you standing outside.
Exactly. You say yes, and you say no.
Standing in the rain with your bad shirt
There is no way you can compare me
And for once, it was you standing outside.
it is because I am exhausted from taking
is because I am exhausted from taking care
of everything that I have to do the
I ever wanted to have sex with you.
I don't think I ever wanted to have
everything that I have to do the next
Oh, you're threatening me with no sex, please.
I don't know when I'll be in the
How will I ever resist my baser instincts?
That'll be good when you come back saying
You expect me to believe that you didn't
expect me to believe that you didn't realize
that we went 26 days without having sex?
I've just had a lot on my mind.
You expect me to believe that you didn't
Guess I was never really close to having
when you use the remote to change the
one of your legs outside of the covers
every so often you kind of sigh a
so often you kind of sigh a little.
You just got a little of your power
I've been waiting for this for a long
Hey, you guys can make breakfast yourself, right?
Daddy has to talk to Mommy upstairs about