Hey, good morning.
Because I thought you were coming right up,
Yeah, the game.
It was amazing.
Because I thought you were coming right up,
Sorry.
Did you catch the end of that game?
See?
All right.
Well, I'll let you boys talk about your
I just hope there's not a game on
Sex.
I think she just gave me the look.
I thought it meant gas.
it's weird though it's weird okay last night i got the look but i i got caught up in the game
though it's weird okay last night i got
it's weird though it's weird okay last night
weird okay last night i got the look
but i i got caught up in the
so i stayed up to watch instead of
going upstairs and now instead of being mad
instead of being mad deborah gave me the
look again huh maybe maybe i should turn her down again you know why would you do a silly thing like
look again huh maybe maybe i should turn
maybe i should turn her down again you
know why would you do a silly thing
that i don't know i mean i'm always
i mean i'm always the one being shot
down it felt good her wondering where i
last night you can't turn her down i
you can't turn her down i could turn
oh come on you'll follow her around like
a dog with his tongue hanging out yeah
your tongue is the leash she uses to
leash she uses to parade you around the
[Laughing]
park ladies and gentlemen worst in show yeah well then uh maybe that's why i should turn her down
park ladies and gentlemen worst in show yeah
worst in show yeah well then uh maybe
uh maybe that's why i should turn her
so she doesn't take me for granted you
i mean she's got to appreciate what she's
what she's got here yes you're quite a
i can hardly keep my hands off you
hey
oh i left the hallway light on
i can say no i can say no
i'll be right back
you must be tired oh yeah i'm kind
uh-oh
i'm kind of beat you know i just
you know i just i got a lot
going on
maybe tomorrow
really
yeah
okay
well night yeah oh good night
wait man come on let's go uh i
uh i don't think i'm gonna go hit
what oh why did the wife say you can't go no no it's just uh just a little stiff that's all
why did the wife say you can't go
it's just uh just a little stiff that's
so it's a medical decision you're making to
a medical decision you're making to stay here
stay here and helping me pick out drapes
ah drapes yeah well there's any material left over once you make yourself a little skirt
ah drapes yeah well there's any material left
over once you make yourself a little skirt
i'm still gonna go and you know what
i may go tomorrow because i can do
you thought i couldn't turn down deborah right
turn down deborah right two times my friend
last night i told her that i had
i had a lot of work to do
work
and then and then first thing this morning
first thing this morning she started hinting again
and then first thing this morning she started
she even brushed your teeth and everything
oh it's amazing it's like it's like every
like it's like every time i turn it
turn it down she seems to want it
oh it's amazing it's like it's like every
huh but she's not getting upset
no no that's just she's so fiscal
down this morning, she was making me a
morning, she was making me a cheese omelet.
I mean, she hasn't done that since before
I mean, yeah, it had shells in it,
You know what I've discovered?
Oh, the power of no. Give me a
hey, who gets to hit a bucket of
You know, you like to golf by yourself
and have a crappy omelet, while I prefer
power of no comes the power of yes.
No, man, you're not getting it.
Deborah can't keep her hands off me.
It's like with the power of no comes
Uh-huh.
You have a wrong.
No, no, no, no, no, no, I don't.
But let me ask you something.
to be manipulative when it comes to sex?
Because I'm not very good at it.
Not very good at what?
Hey, listen, Robert, he can't go hit balls,
but I was thinking that I'd still go.
Yeah, sure, go. Have a good time.
Hey, you let me be the one to
They got a great hot dog guy there.
You want me to bring you back one?
let me be the one to watch your
Hey, you let me be the one to
Hey, you let me be the one to watch your figure.
let me be the one to watch your
That's right, it's not, and yet it is.
Because she is weak.
Weak for my physique.
[Clattering]
Oh.
I don't know why Robert had such a
Oh, don't those look nice?
putting them up yesterday.
Well, he can't handle normal-sized tools
with those giant fingers.
I don't know why Robert had such a
So what do you think, Deb?
Yeah, they look great.
Deborah, dear, you're being so quiet.
That's not like you.
No, I'm fine.
Do I look different to you?
What do you mean?
Have I drooped?
Drooped?
You know, you try to work out
and yet there still comes a day
[Mimics exploding sound]
when everything just...
I wouldn't know about that.
You know how my friends and I keep
Water aerobics at the Y.
Say, why don't you come with us tomorrow?
I'll have to check and see if I'm
Oh, well, I'll have to check and see
Let me go look for an extra pair
Deb, are you really upset about this?
Ray keeps turning me down.
He usually follows you around with his tongue
Yeah.
I know.
I'm sure it's not you.
I should just go with Marie to the
I should just go with Marie to the Y,
Hey, you know,
because last night when Robert and I went
he was acting kind of distant, too.
And then he said something about how I
and he said, Ray's crazy.
something about how I could have all the
It was weird.
Yeah, he usually doesn't like to mention Ray
And then he said something about how I
Oh, my God.
Yeah, he usually doesn't like to mention Ray
The power is in the upper hand or something.
The power is in the upper hand or
Well, that's gross.
You know, the worst part about this is
Do you know I did 138 sit ups
the worst part about this is that it
I've been trying to make myself look better
Do you know I did 138 sit ups
this morning all for some guy whose stomach
all for some guy whose stomach looks like
Boy, boy.
You're gonna kill him, aren't you?
No.
Hey, Jimmy Jack.
Hey. How was work?
I didn't think it would be appropriate for
I sent them over to the Parker's.
I wanted them out of the house.
I didn't think it would be appropriate for
to see what I was going to do
to see what I was going to do to you.
I didn't think it would be appropriate for
I mean, I got a lot to do.
I just can't resist a man with so
Yeah, yeah, well...
Okay, look, I'm really starting to feel a
[screams]
Okay, look, I'm really starting to feel a little uncomfortable.
What's with you?
Robert told Amy why you've been turning me
Robert told Amy why you've been turning me down.
So you were just toying with me?
to be the one being pursued for once.
But you made me feel terrible about myself.
I guess I wanted to see what it
I wanted to see what it was like
to be the one being pursued for once.
But you made me feel terrible about myself.
I guess I wanted to see what it
How could you do that to somebody?
You had me convinced I was a fat,
bad because I turned you down, what, three
Try being rejected 40 or 50 times every
for the last ten years.
no way I turn you down that much.
How do you think that feels?
You're looking at the president
Welcome. Have a doughnut.
There is no way I turn you down
Exactly. You say yes, and you say no.
You're the bouncer in front of the disco
who decides who gets in and who doesn't.
And for once, it was you standing outside.
Exactly. You say yes, and you say no.
Yeah, and you couldn't take it.
Standing in the rain with your bad shirt
There is no way you can compare me
And for once, it was you standing outside.
it is because I am exhausted from taking
of everything that I have to do the
Still using the kids, huh?
think I ever wanted to have sex with
I don't think I ever wanted to have
that I have to do the next day.
Oh, you're threatening me with no sex, please.
I don't know when I'll be in the
I'm serious.
You wouldn't last a night.
I don't know when I'll be in the
Okay, so we'll see who can't last.
Oh, my.
How will I ever resist my baser instincts?
That'll be good when you come back saying
Okay, well, good enough.
[groans]
Ugh.
Oh, my God.
Are those silk?
You want a feel?
It's quite all right.
What's with all your lacy apparel?
Nothing.
Good night.
Yeah.
[Groans]
I'm a little tired, too.
Did you put oil on?
No.
What are you doing?
Me?
What'd you have my mom put on?
Your makeup on?
No sex for you.
[Jazzy lounge music]
¶¶
What?
I give up!
I am officially asking you to please
What are you talking about?
Our thing!
Our not-having-sex thing!
Of course we're still doing it.
It's been 26 days of doing it.
Not doing it!
Yeah, right!
You expect me to believe that you didn't
I can't believe it, but really,
I totally forgot.
You expect me to believe that you didn't
that we went 26 days without having sex?
I've just had a lot on my mind.
You expect me to believe that you didn't
26 days?
You weren't even trying.
Guess I was never really close to having
was I?
All this time,
Guess I was never really close to having
little things to torture me.
What things?
Forget it.
when you use the remote to change the
one of your legs outside of the covers
when you use the remote to change the channel.
and the pajama rides up it?
every so often you kind of sigh a
[Sighs quietly]
every so often you kind of sigh a little.
every so often you kind of sigh a
You haven't slept much lately, have you?
Even now,
look at you,
with your hair like that,
with your...
robe.
What a mess!
Yeah, well,
You just got a little of your power
You just got a little of your power back.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.
You just got a little of your power
I've been waiting for this for a long
it's been 27 days, not 26.
Remember.
Morning, kids.
Well, you live here.
No!
Hey, you guys can make breakfast yourself, right?
has to talk to Mommy upstairs about something.
Eh?
[Mumbles weakly]